Love is Near
Cross Life is a drama film directed by Claire McCarthy.
Ten fragments of life.
Three days until Christmas.
Cross Life is a tale of ordinary people pained by the desire for love amidst the
sensual delights of Sydney's red light district, Kings Cross.
Bill, played by Tony Barry.
Donald, played by Mojean Aria.
Joe, played by Paul Caesar.
Zana, played by Imogen Annesley.
Thomas, played by Paul W. He.
Married Life is a 2007 American period drama film directed by Ira Sachs.
The screenplay by Sachs and Oren Moverman is based on the 1953
novel Five Roundabouts to Heaven by John Bingham.
Cast members include Patricia Clarkson, Chris Cooper,
Rachel McAdams and Pierce Brosnan.
The novel was also the basis for the December 20, 1962 episode of The
Alfred Hitchcock Hour entitled "The Tender Poisoner".
The tone is emotional.